export const natureQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    heading: "First question",
    question:
      "How much plastic do you think the avarage person consumes in a month?",
    correct_answer: "1",
    incorrect_answer: ["2", "3"],
    correct_prompt: "Correct! Sadly it takes between 80-100 years for a single aluminium can to decompose. At Ricola we have as a target to reduce waste by 7 % (50 tonnes) for 2021.",
    incorrect_prompt: "Damn it, you’re close! Actually it’s about 8.8 million tons. At Ricola we try our best to reduce the plastic in our packaging and experimenting using waste material from our production. Did you know? The amount of plastic dumped in our oceans is equivalent to one garbage truck every minute.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    heading: "Second question",
    question: "How much Co2 is released into the atmosphere everywhere?",
    correct_answer: "1",
    incorrect_answer: ["2", "3"],
    correct_prompt: " HELLO Correct! Sadly it takes between 80-100 years for a single aluminium can to decompose. At Ricola we have as a target to reduce waste by 7 % (50 tonnes) for 2021.",
    incorrect_prompt: "Damn it, you’re close! Actually it’s about 8.8 million tons. At Ricola we try our best to reduce the plastic in our packaging and experimenting using waste material from our production. Did you know? The amount of plastic dumped in our oceans is equivalent to one garbage truck every minute.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    heading: "Third question",
    question:
      "How much plastic do you think the avarage person consumes in a month?",
    correct_answer: "1",
    incorrect_answer: ["2", "3"],
    correct_prompt: "Correct! Sadly it takes between 80-100 years for a single aluminium can to decompose. At Ricola we have as a target to reduce waste by 7 % (50 tonnes) for 2021.",
    incorrect_prompt: "Damn it, you’re close! Actually it’s about 8.8 million tons. At Ricola we try our best to reduce the plastic in our packaging and experimenting using waste material from our production. Did you know? The amount of plastic dumped in our oceans is equivalent to one garbage truck every minute.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    heading: "Fourth question",
    question: "How much Co2 is released into the atmosphere everywhere?",
    correct_answer: "1",
    incorrect_answer: ["2", "3"],
    correct_prompt: "Correct! Sadly it takes between 80-100 years for a single aluminium can to decompose. At Ricola we have as a target to reduce waste by 7 % (50 tonnes) for 2021.",
    incorrect_prompt: "Damn it, you’re close! Actually it’s about 8.8 million tons. At Ricola we try our best to reduce the plastic in our packaging and experimenting using waste material from our production. Did you know? The amount of plastic dumped in our oceans is equivalent to one garbage truck every minute.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    heading: "Fifth question",
    question:
      "How much plastic do you think the avarage person consumes in a month?",
    correct_answer: "1",
    incorrect_answer: ["2", "3"],
    correct_prompt: "Correct! Sadly it takes between 80-100 years for a single aluminium can to decompose. At Ricola we have as a target to reduce waste by 7 % (50 tonnes) for 2021.",
    incorrect_prompt: "Damn it, you’re close! Actually it’s about 8.8 million tons. At Ricola we try our best to reduce the plastic in our packaging and experimenting using waste material from our production. Did you know? The amount of plastic dumped in our oceans is equivalent to one garbage truck every minute.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    heading: "Sixth question",
    question: "How much Co2 is released into the atmosphere everywhere?",
    correct_answer: "1",
    incorrect_answer: ["2", "3"],
    correct_prompt: "Correct! Sadly it takes between 80-100 years for a single aluminium can to decompose. At Ricola we have as a target to reduce waste by 7 % (50 tonnes) for 2021.",
    incorrect_prompt: "Damn it, you’re close! Actually it’s about 8.8 million tons. At Ricola we try our best to reduce the plastic in our packaging and experimenting using waste material from our production. Did you know? The amount of plastic dumped in our oceans is equivalent to one garbage truck every minute.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    heading: "Seventh question",
    question: "How much Co2 is released into the atmosphere everywhere?",
    correct_answer: "1",
    incorrect_answer: ["2", "3"],
    correct_prompt: "Correct! Sadly it takes between 80-100 years for a single aluminium can to decompose. At Ricola we have as a target to reduce waste by 7 % (50 tonnes) for 2021.",
    incorrect_prompt: "Damn it, you’re close! Actually it’s about 8.8 million tons. At Ricola we try our best to reduce the plastic in our packaging and experimenting using waste material from our production. Did you know? The amount of plastic dumped in our oceans is equivalent to one garbage truck every minute.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    heading: "Congratulations!",
    question: "You completed the Ricola quiz and climbed to the top of the mountain! Share your results with your friends for a chance to win a year supply of Ricola products. #ricolafootsteps.",
    correct_answer: "",
    incorrect_answer: "",
    correct_prompt: "",
    incorrect_answer: "",
  },
];
